# Sujay Mahadik

Pune, Maharashtra, India



mahadik203@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/sujay-mahadik

## **Summary**

I am often found juggling with interests that include coding, graphic design, all the way to appreciating good coffee and nerding out over pop fiction, astrophysics and dystopian literature. I have 4 years of experience in full stack front end development, illustrations, graphics and motion design.

Pursuing Masters in Economics from Ferguson College under Pune Uni's Open Learning Programme

## Experience



## **Co-Founder and Designer**

The Jellyfish Collective

Jun 2020 - Present (4 months +)

Co-Founded a remote, non-conforming design collective based in Paris focused on creating visual identity. Our collective has experience in diverse fields such as design, photography, UI/UX design among a few.



#### **Graduate Analyst**

**Barclays** 

Aug 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months +)

Working with Barclays around Enterprise and Data Integration Infrastruture Administration

ETL tools include Informatica and Ab Initio



#### **Graphic Designer**

Infin8y Labs

Sep 2016 - May 2020 (3 years 9 months)

A hobby venture revolving around Graphic Design.



#### **Project Intern**

Persistent Systems

Sep 2017 - Jun 2018 (10 months)

The aim of the project was to create an Autonomous Drone and was done in a group of 6 students. The project involved working with cutting edge hardware technology.

I was looking after the simulation and designing terrains in Unity 3D Game Engine



#### **Design and Technical Head**

MIT CREON

Aug 2016 - Feb 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Web-Dev of MIT CREON 17, MIT CREON 18 along with graphic design of publicity boards and posters. The project also included an SMTP server ticket booking platform for an event.

### **Education**

Fergusson College

Master of Arts - MA, Economics 2019 - 2021

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering (BE) , Information Technology 2015 - 2019 MIT College of Enginnering Among Top 5 in the department

Pace Junior Science College

HSC, Science 2013 - 2015 Among Top 1%, Awarded research scholarship

National English School, ICSE
ICSE

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- **Python** Spoken Tutorial, IIT Bombay
- PHP MySQL Spoken Tutorial, IIT Bombay
- Arduino Spoken Tutorial, IIT Bombay
- Blockchain Basics by University of Buffalo & The State University of New York Coursera
  T682MSQWQARE
- Smart Contracts by University at Buffalo & The State University of New York Coursera GXN2XRK95XUT
- Internet Connection Cisco Networking Academy
  LTKPEEDADCK4
- Network Protocols and Architecture Cisco Networking Academy
  8ALZDM48SYWG
- The Data Scientist's Toolbox by Johns Hopkins University Coursera

#### TPW5HGAGFFE9

Textual Elements of Design: Fonts, Typography, and Spacing by University of Colorado

Boulder - Coursera
76XEHZZWN3GY

Print and Digital Elements of Design: Branding and User Experience by University of Colorado Boulder - Coursera

YP9CNVY3NPF9

Introduction to Philosophy by The University of Edinburgh - Coursera

M6SQT8L2KABN

#### **Skills**

JavaScript • Graphic Design • Game Development • HTML • React.js • Adobe Illustrator • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • Web Design • User Interface Design

#### **Honors & Awards**

- Scholarship for Higher Education, Top 1% in Boards Maharashtra State Board of Secondary and Higher Education Society

  Mar 2015
- Primary School Scholarship
- International Olympiad of Mathematics 2008